abercrombiekids.com 2014-11-20

# Customer Service | abercrombiekids.com

## abercrombie kids  us  
PRIVACY POLICY

Updated: June 2014

This privacy policy statement applies only to the information collected online through abercrombiekids.com, microsites, or mobile sites of abercrombie kids that expressly adopt, display or link to, this policy (our “Websites”).  To help your understanding, we provide this explanation of what information our Websites collect online, and how our Websites use the information.

abercrombie kids encourages families to use and explore the Internet together. We have implemented procedures to avoid collecting, using or disclosing personal information of guests under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian.

We limit the collection of personal information about children under 13 on our Websites to that which is reasonably necessary to enable them to participate in the activities that we offer on our Websites.

## Contents

Information Collected Online  
Using Information We Collect Online  
Information We Share With Third Parties  
Cookies  
Opt Out  
International Users  
Updating Personal Information In Your Account  
Links  
Updates to Privacy Policy  
Security Statement  
Supported Web Browsers  
Questions/Contact Us

## Information Collected Online

### 1\. General Browsing

We collect general information about our visitors’ experience with our Websites and this general information is not connected to personally identifiable information about individual visitors. The information collected includes which pages our visitors are viewing on our Websites and whether visitors arrived through a link for our Websites.  It also includes information on the type of browser and service provider used.  For visitors using a mobile version of our Websites, this includes technical information about the device used, such as screen size, cookie support by the device and how images may appear.   All of this information helps us provide a better experience for our visitors by being able to determine such things as how to best format our mobile Websites for various devices, our most desired pages, products and features, how to best direct visitors to our Websites, and where there might be browser or service provider connection issues.

### 2\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information if You Are 13 or Older

abercrombie kids collects personally identifiable information from you when you voluntarily provide us with this information. You can provide us this personally identifiable information in many instances throughout our Websites, for example when you interact with the following opportunities: placing an order through our Websites; establishing an account; adding your choices and information about yourself and others to your account; emailing an item, post card or wish list; adding a message in the gift wrap section or on an E-Gift Card; entering a contest or sweepstakes (note that some contests or sweepstakes may require the parent/guardian of an individual 13 or older but under 18 to submit an entry using the process described below in "Contest or Sweepstakes Entries"); taking a survey; contacting us with a comment or question; and signing up to receive emails about our products and services.

Categories of personally identifiable information collected online include name, address, email address, telephone number, payment card information, child's name, address and email address, recipient's name, address and email address, purchases you make tied to your personally identifiable information, and any other information you choose to provide, including through your personal social media accounts, as described below.

Personal Information You Allow Us to Collect from Your Social Media Accounts.  To create an account on our Websites or to participate in certain features, our Websites may allow you to chose to let us access information from accounts you have created on social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Instagram and other similar sites ("Personal Social Media Accounts"). If you chose to allow us access to your Personal Social Media Accounts, abercrombie kids could collect some, and possibly all, of the data in the Personal Social Media Account to which you grant access.  Depending on the terms of the social media site, this information could include: your name, email address, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID, list of friends, birthday, likes, education history, work history, current city, hometown, interests, relationship status, location. Once you grant this permission, abercrombie kids will be able to continue to be linked to the permitted Personal Social Media Account and collect information without a further request for permission, which could include later revisions to existing information or new types of information that you add.  If you no longer want your Personal Social Media Account(s) linked to our Websites, click on the ‘disconnect’ link located on our Websites near the corresponding social media button and we will stop collecting this information.  You may also be able to stop our ability to link to information in your Personal Social Media Account by following instructions provided on the applicable social media site. 

This privacy policy does not cover the privacy and security practices of social media sites where you have Personal Social Media Accounts. Please review privacy policies and terms of service on the social media sites if you have any questions about their privacy or security practices.

### 3\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information for Children Under 13

If you are under 13 and want to sign up for email marketing or enter a contest or sweepstakes, we have implemented the following processes:

**Mailing List Registration**

With regard to the general "Mailing List" registration at our Websites, we have a separate "Mailing List" registration process for kids who state that they are under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 will only be asked to provide their first name, age, and parent's/guardian's email address. abercrombie kids will then send the parent/guardian an email notice and a request that the parent complete the "Mailing List" sign up for their child. After abercrombie kids sends the email notice to the parent to request that the parent complete the "Mailing List" sign up and consent, abercrombie kids does not add the child's name or age, or the email address of the parent provided by the child to its systems (however, if the parent has separately signed up for email, that email address may be in our systems). Before the child can receive emails and other promotional materials from abercrombie kids, the child's parent/guardian must consent by completing the child's "Mailing List" registration information. Whenever a parent/guardian completes and submits the child's "Mailing List" registration information, abercrombie kids will send the parent/guardian a confirmation email notification.

If a parent/guardian does not wish to consent by completing their child's "Mailing List" registration with abercrombie kids, the parent/guardian may decline completing the "Mailing List" sign up and consent. Should a parent/guardian initially consent to their child's registration by completing the "Mailing List" registration, they can cancel that consent at any time and request deletion of their child's personal information by emailing such a request to abercrombie kids at [privacy_policy@abercrombiekids.com](mailto:Privacy_Policy@abercrombiekids.com).

**Contest or Sweepstakes Entries**

For each contest or sweepstakes we conduct for children who indicate that they are under the age of 13 (or other age as specified in the official rules for the contest or sweepstakes), we will only collect a child's first name and a parent's/guardian's email address. abercrombie kids will then send the parent/guardian an email notice and a request that the parent complete the "Contest or Sweepstakes" sign-up for their child. After abercrombie kids sends the email notice to the parent to request that the parent complete the "Contest or Sweepstakes" entry form and consent, abercrombie kids does not add the child's name or age, or the email address of the parent provided by the child to its systems (however, if the parent has separately signed up for email, that email address may be in our systems). Before the child will be entered in the contest or sweepstakes, the child's parent/guardian must consent by completing the child's "Contest or Sweepstakes" registration information.

If a parent/guardian does not wish to consent to their child's entry into the "Contest or Sweepstakes" with abercrombie kids, the parent/guardian may decline completing the "Contest or Sweepstakes" entry form and consent. The “Contest or Sweepstakes” entry form and consent may also allow a parent/guardian to register their child to receive ongoing emails and other promotional materials from abercrombie kids. Should a parent/guardian initially consent by completing the "Contest or Sweepstakes" entry form and consent or by electing to register their child to receive ongoing emails and other promotional materials from abercrombie kids, the parent/guardian can cancel that consent at any time and request deletion of their child's personal information by emailing such a request to abercrombie kids at [privacy_policy@abercrombiekids.com](mailto:Privacy_Policy@abercrombiekids.com).

**Review of Information Provided About a Child**

For parents/guardians who have completed their child's "Mailing List" or "Contest" or "Sweepstakes" registration, they can review the personally-identifiable information they provided about their child online by sending an email to [privacy_policy@abercrombiekids.com](mailto:privacy_policy@abercrombiekids.com), or a letter or postcard to the postal mailing address provided under "Contact Us" below. When making a written request to review such information, please be sure to include your email address and telephone number where we can reach you. To protect your child's privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the personal information that you provide and we maintain about your child.

### 4\. Information Collected within the "A&F Credit Card" Link on the Website

If you apply online for an Abercrombie & Fitch credit card, or once opened, access your account online (to pay your account, view your statement or account status, add authorized buyers to your account, request a credit limit increase or update the personal information associated with your account) you leave our Websites and provide your personal information directly to the issuing bank for the Abercrombie & Fitch Card. However, your name, address, and email address, as well as information necessary for us to provide you with the bonuses and benefits of an Abercrombie & Fitch Card (which may include birth date, payment card number, and purchasing information), will be provided to us by the Abercrombie & Fitch Card issuer. We would suggest that you review the privacy policies of these third parties prior to providing them with your information.

## Using Information We Collect Online

**Children under 13** : If a parent submits his or her child's personal information as specified in the section "Mailing List Registration" above, it will be used only for the purpose of sending promotional materials to his or her child.

A child's personal information submitted by a parent/guardian as specified in the section "Contest or Sweepstakes Entries" above will only be used for the purpose of entering the child into the contest or sweepstakes for which the information was submitted, unless the parent/guardian elects to register their child to receive ongoing promotional materials from abercrombie kids as specified in the section “Contest or Sweepstakes Entries” above. If a parent/guardian elects to register his or her child, the child’s personal information will be used only for the purpose of sending promotional materials.

**If you are 13 or over:** abercrombie kids uses the information collected on Our Websites, to fulfill product orders; to fulfill your requests (such as contact us, click to chat, email a friend, wish list, entering you in a contest or sweepstakes or sending a post card); to update information maintained in your online account; to contact you or the product recipient(s) in the event of order or delivery difficulties; to serve site content; to analyze your activity with us, including interactions with our Websites, the effectiveness of our advertising and your purchases; to provide marketing communications regarding our products, services, and promotions to you and to people in your account address book; to personalize our communications to you; to respond to your inquiries; to conduct surveys, sweepstakes or contests; and to develop our products, services, and our Websites. See the "Opt-Out" section below for the choices you have related to receiving marketing communications from Us.

If you created an account on or after June 28, 2012, any information you submit in your address book will be used for marketing purposes. If you have an account and are signed in at the time of your visit, we will use information you entered into a Wish List for promotional purposes.  If you do not have an account, any information you entered into a Wish List is not used for any promotional purposes by us or our affiliated companies.  Please keep in mind, however, that we will send promotional communications to your Wish List recipients if they have separately agreed to receive promotional communications from us. 

## Information We Share With Third Parties

abercrombie kids does not sell, rent or trade the personal information about children under the age of 13 knowingly obtained from parents/guardians online at our Websites to anyone.  For visitors 13 and older, abercrombie kids may make the following information available to our affiliates and other unaffiliated companies for their marketing purposes: your name and address information, sometimes categorized by purchasing information; and, if you create an account on or after June 28, 2012, any information you submit in your account address book. See the "Opt-Out" section below for instructions on how to opt out of sharing with unaffiliated companies.

If you are 13 and older, when you provide us your email, you elect to share your email address with our affiliated companies (for example, Abercrombie & Fitch, Hollister Co., and Gilly Hicks) so that they may send you promotional materials, we will share your email address with them. You can be assured that except for similar limited circumstances as specified below and also in their privacy policies, our affiliated companies will not sell or rent your email address to unrelated third parties.

Please be aware that we may use third parties to assist us with our Websites and e-commerce business, such as our Websites and emails, and our Social Media Pages. Some examples of the assistance that may be provided by third party service providers are: fulfilling orders (including but not limited to, processing payments, providing fraud prevention services, and verifying addresses); providing advertising services, including on social media sites and internet search engines; monitoring and analyzing site activity; conducting surveys; and administering emails, promotions, sweepstakes or contests. Personal information you provide us may be shared, as necessary, directly with the relevant third parties to so carry our functions on our behalf. It is possible that some of these service providers will be located outside of the United States.

You should also be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if necessary to do so by law or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law or is necessary to protect the users of our Websites, the Websites or the public.

If abercrombie kids were ever merged with or acquired by another company, or if it acquires another business entity or is involved in a corporate reorganization or other change of control, some or all of the personal information collected about visitors 13 or older would be shared with this entity, as well as retained by abercrombie kids. Other than this acquisition, sale or reorganization, we do not sell or rent your email address to unrelated third parties.

## Cookies

### 1\. What Are Cookies and How Do We Use Them?

Our Websites use a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer. The cookies are typically stored on your computer's hard drive or mobile device. Information collected from cookies is used by abercrombie kids to evaluate the effectiveness of our Websites, analyze trends, and administer our Websites. The information collected from cookies allows us to determine such things as which parts of our Websites are most visited and difficulties our visitors may experience in accessing our Websites. With this knowledge, we can improve the quality of your experience on our Websites by recognizing and delivering more of the most desired features and information, as well as by resolving access difficulties. In addition, our Websites use cookies to make recommendations for other products on our Websites by associating cookies that do not include any personal information with specific items viewed, put in shopping carts or purchased.  Cookies that do not include any personal information also allow the ability to maintain shopping carts between visits. Our Websites also use cookies to help keep track of checkout information, other than payment method information, while you remain on our Websites.

### 2\. Third Party Cookies

We use third party service provider(s) to assist us in better understanding the use of our Websites. Our service provider(s) will place cookies on your computer and will receive information that we select that will educate us on such things as how visitors navigate around our Websites, what features are most used, what products are browsed, aggregate purchasing information, and if a search engine was used or advertisement clicked to navigate to our Websites. Our service provider(s) analyzes this information and provides us with aggregate reports. The information and analysis provided by our service provider(s) will be used to assist us in better understanding our visitors' interests in our Websites and how to better serve those interests.

If you have an account and are signed in at the time of your visit, our service providers use cookies to collect information regarding your activity on our Websites so that we can better understand your interests and send you personalized communications.  Unless you have an account, we do not associate the information collected by our service provider(s) with information that we collect about you while you are visiting our Websites.

## Opt-Out

To make it easier for you, we have moved your opt-out preference choices to this section of the privacy policy.

Children under 13: **** If your parent/guardian has signed you up to receive abercrombie kids email,  you may unsubscribe or chose to limit the frequency at which you receive marketing emails by going to the unsubscribe page.

Parents/guardians of children under 13:  See section “3. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information for Children Under 13” above for information regarding withdrawing your consent.  

If you are 13 or older:

  1. Email.  You can choose the frequency at which you receive marketing emails or unsubscribe if you no longer want to receive marketing emails from abercrombie kids, or our affiliated companies (like Abercrombie & Fitch, Hollister Co. or Gilly Hicks).  To unsubscribe from abercrombie kids go to the unsubscribe page, or to unsubscribe from our affiliated companies go to the email and phone page within the “My Account” or "My Info" section of the Websites, click on "manage your marketing preferences", and select the option to no longer receive emails in the dropdown menus for each brand, and press ‘SUBMIT.' Please be aware, however, even if you request to limit the frequency you can receive marketing emails or to be removed from our marketing list, you may still receive email confirmations for any orders placed on our Websites. 
  2. Postal Marketing.  If you no longer wish to receive marketing materials from abercrombie kids via regular postal mail, please email us at [privacy_policy@abercrombiekids.com](mailto:privacy_policy@abercrombiekids.com) and tell us that you want to be removed from the postal mailing list, including the postal address you wish to have removed.
  3. Third-Party Postal Address Sharing.  You can request that we do not disclose your name and postal address or, if you created an account on or after June 28, 2012, a name and postal address in your account address book to unaffiliated third parties for their marketing purposes. Please email us at [privacy_policy@abercrombiekids.com](mailto:privacy_policy@abercrombiekids.com) and ask us not to share your postal address or a name and address in your account address book with unaffiliated companies, including the specific name and postal address.  Please be aware, however, even if you request that we do not share a name and postal address in your account address book, we may share the name and postal address if that person has separately provided their information to us.

## International Users

If you are visiting our Websites from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States, your orders placed through our Websites will be accepted and processed in and shipped from the United States, and information that you provide will be processed and maintained by us in our Web servers and internal systems located within the United States. This privacy policy governs the information collected by or on behalf of our Websites irrespective of where you are located when you access it, browse it interact with it, and make purchases through it (including those that are shipped to addresses outside the US). This means your personal information may be stored outside of the province, state, and/or country in which you reside, and processed by us, an affiliate or a third party service provider as described in this privacy policy. Moreover, governmental bodies that have jurisdiction over us in the United States (e.g., courts and law enforcement agencies) may be entitled to access your personal information.

## Updating Personal Information In Your Account

If you have created an online account, we prefer to keep your personal information accurate and up-to-date. To do this, we provide you with the opportunity to update or modify your personal information, including your billing address, preferred shipping information, payment details, and contact information. Just sign in to your account with your email address and password, and you will see an overview page where you can update your information.

To request to have your account cancelled send an email to [Privacy_Policy@abercrombiekids.com](mailto:privacy_policy@abercrombiekids.com) and include the email address of the account you wish to cancel.

## Links

For your convenience and enjoyment, our Websites may contain links to other websites. abercrombie kids does not disclose any personally identifiable information or non-personally identifiable information received by abercrombie kids to these other websites. abercrombie kids does not evaluate and is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites. We would urge you to review the privacy policies on each link to ensure you are comfortable with their privacy policies and practices.

## Updates to Privacy Policy

As we continue to offer you new and different types of content and services, abercrombie kids may modify our information collection, use or disclosure practices. Should there be a material change to our information practices, it will be applied only to information collected on a going forward basis, and we will update this privacy policy statement. For children under the age of 13 for whom parents have already given consent, abercrombie kids will send a new notice and request for parental consent before any new collections of personally identifiable information occurs and/or any new uses of previously collected personally identifiable information occurs that are not detailed in this privacy policy.

## Security Statement

abercrombie kids limits the number of employees who have access to the databases that contain personal information, and abercrombie kids employees are advised of the importance of confidentiality. In addition, it is our policy to never send payment card numbers via email.

We designed our Websites to accept orders only from Web browsers that permit communication through Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology; Browsers that do not meet this requirement will be prevented from navigating the online store section of our Websites. See "Supported Web Browsers" for more information. While we implement the above security measures on our Websites, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible.

## Supported Web Browsers

abercrombie kids supports the following Web browsers: Mozilla Firefox 3.6+, Microsoft Internet Explorer 7.0+, Google Chrome 14.0+, and Apple Safari 5.0+. Additionally, some of our Websites content requires Adobe Flash Player 9.0 or later.

## Questions/Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our privacy policy and/or privacy practices, please email us at [privacy_policy@abercrombiekids.com](mailto:Privacy_Policy@abercrombiekids.com) or write to us at the following address:

Attn: Privacy Policy Manager  
Abercrombie & Fitch Stores, Inc.  
6301 Fitch Path  
New Albany, Ohio 43054 USA
